areacellphone.com 2012-06-26

# iPad, iPhone, Motorola Droid and Android Phones Apps | areacellphone.com

Privacy Policy – http://areacellphone.com

Privacy Policy for http://areacellphone.com

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at **admin@areacellphone.com**.

At areacellphone.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by areacellphone.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, areacellphone.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
areacellphone.com does not use cookies.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on areacellphone.com.  
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to areacellphone.com and other sites on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….  
Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on areacellphone.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

areacellphone.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. areacellphone.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

  * [Samsung Jet S8003: How To Enable GPS Navigation And Navigation Route 66 For Free](http://areacellphone.com/2009/09/samsung-s8003-enable-gps-route66-free/ "Samsung Jet S8003: How To Enable GPS Navigation And Navigation Route 66 For Free")
  * [Samsung Behold: How To Install Java Games And Apps Like Google Maps, Gmail And Opera](http://areacellphone.com/2009/10/samsung-behold-howto-java-apps/ "Samsung Behold: How To Install Java Games And Apps Like Google Maps, Gmail And Opera")
  * [iPhone Vs HTC EVO: 4G Can Succeed Where Droid And Nexus Failed](http://areacellphone.com/2010/03/iphone-vs-htc-evo-4g-droid-nexus-failed/ "iPhone Vs HTC EVO: 4G Can Succeed Where Droid And Nexus Failed")
  * [Motorola Droid: Download 10 Top Android Apps You Must Have On Your Droid](http://areacellphone.com/2009/11/motorola-droid-download-10-top-android-apps/ "Motorola Droid: Download 10 Top Android Apps You Must Have On Your Droid")
  * [Top Android Security Apps: Antivirus, Spam Blocker And Anti Malware](http://areacellphone.com/2010/05/top-android-security-apps-antivirus-spam-blocker-anti-malware/ "Top Android Security Apps: Antivirus, Spam Blocker And Anti Malware")
  * [How To Set Android Wifi: Solve Weak Signal And Dropped Connections](http://areacellphone.com/2010/04/how-to-set-android-wifi-solve-weak-signal-dropped-connections/ "How To Set Android Wifi: Solve Weak Signal And Dropped Connections")
  * [First iOS 5 Untethered Jailbreak For iPhone 3GS: Unlock Via UltraSn0w](http://areacellphone.com/2011/06/first-ios-5-untethered-jailbreak-for-iphone-3gs-unlock-via-ultrasn0w/ "First iOS 5 Untethered Jailbreak For iPhone 3GS: Unlock Via UltraSn0w")
  * [Installing Android 2.1 On Windows Mobile Phone Is Possible But Not Perfect](http://areacellphone.com/2010/02/installing-android-2-1-on-windows-mobile-phone-is-possible-but-not-perfect/ "Installing Android 2.1 On Windows Mobile Phone Is Possible But Not Perfect")
  * [Download Nokia Symbian Need For Speed Undercover For 5800XM And N97](http://areacellphone.com/2009/09/download-nokia-symbian-undercover/ "Download Nokia Symbian Need For Speed Undercover For 5800XM And N97")
  * [Download Free Latest Version Mobile Number Locator 3.1 For India](http://areacellphone.com/2009/11/download-free-latest-mobile-number-locator-india/ "Download Free Latest Version Mobile Number Locator 3.1 For India")
  * [Cell Phone Antenna Signal Boosters: How To Install To Get Better Reception](http://areacellphone.com/2009/11/cell-phone-antenna-boosters-how-to-install-reception/ "Cell Phone Antenna Signal Boosters: How To Install To Get Better Reception")
  * [Best Bumper Case For iPhone 4: Designed To Solve All Design Problems](http://areacellphone.com/2010/07/best-bumper-case-for-iphone-4-designed-to-solve-all-design-problems/ "Best Bumper Case For iPhone 4: Designed To Solve All Design Problems")
  * [Top Nintendo Emulators For N900: Play All Nintendo Games On Nokia N900](http://areacellphone.com/2010/02/top-nintendo-emulators-for-n900-play-all-nintendo-games-on-nokia-n900/ "Top Nintendo Emulators For N900: Play All Nintendo Games On Nokia N900")
  * [Best iPhone Texting App To Keep Your Private Messages Private](http://areacellphone.com/2010/02/best-iphone-texting-app-keep-private-messages-private/ "Best iPhone Texting App To Keep Your Private Messages Private")
  * [Top 10 iPhone Apps And Games May 2010: Augmented Reality App On Top](http://areacellphone.com/2010/05/top-10-iphone-apps-games-may-2010-augmented-reality-app/ "Top 10 iPhone Apps And Games May 2010: Augmented Reality App On Top")
  * [Sony Ericsson YENDO And CEDAR: Bundles Touch TrackID And PlayNow Feature](http://areacellphone.com/2010/06/sony-ericsson-yendo-cedar-bundles-touch-trackid-playnow-feature/ "Sony Ericsson YENDO And CEDAR: Bundles Touch TrackID And PlayNow Feature")
  * [Cydia App To Sync Music To iPad, iPhone Without iTunes Or Computer](http://areacellphone.com/2010/09/cydia-app-sync-music-ipad-iphone-without-itunes-computer/ "Cydia App To Sync Music To iPad, iPhone Without iTunes Or Computer")
  * [Best Android Game For Your Motorola Xoom, Atrix, Thunderbolt This March](http://areacellphone.com/2011/01/best-android-game-for-your-motorola-xoom-atrix-thunderbolt-this-march/ "Best Android Game For Your Motorola Xoom, Atrix, Thunderbolt This March")
  * [Saygus Two Way Video Calling Android Phone For Verizon Is Not Droid](http://areacellphone.com/2009/11/saygus-two-way-video-calling-android-phone-verizon-droid/ "Saygus Two Way Video Calling Android Phone For Verizon Is Not Droid")
  * [Nokia Free GPS Satellite Navigation: Faster Than Google Free GPS App](http://areacellphone.com/2010/01/nokia-free-gps-satellite-navigation-faster-than-google-free-gps-app/ "Nokia Free GPS Satellite Navigation: Faster Than Google Free GPS App")
  * [Top 10 Apps For Jailbroken iPhone: Free From Apple Restrictions](http://areacellphone.com/2010/03/top-10-apps-for-jailbroken-iphone-free-from-apple-restrictions/ "Top 10 Apps For Jailbroken iPhone: Free From Apple Restrictions")
  * [Samsung I9000 Galaxy S Vs HTC HD2: Its OS Not Size That Matters](http://areacellphone.com/2010/03/samsung-i9000-galaxy-s-vs-htc-hd2-os-size/ "Samsung I9000 Galaxy S Vs HTC HD2: Its OS Not Size That Matters")
  * [HTC Evo 4G Vs Motorola Droid: Evo Has Three While Droid Only One](http://areacellphone.com/2010/03/htc-evo-4g-vs-motorola-droid-evo/ "HTC Evo 4G Vs Motorola Droid: Evo Has Three While Droid Only One")

No tags for this post.
